<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="faq_question_1">How can I create a new profile?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_2">How can I delete a profile?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_3">How can I change my email/phone number?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_4">What is Oppia?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_5">Who is an Administrator?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_6">Why is the Exploration player not loading?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_7">Why is my audio not playing?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_8">How do I download a Topic?</string>
  <string name="faq_question_9">I can\'t find my question here. What now?</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_1">\u003cp\u003eIf it is your first time creating a profile and not have a PIN:\u003cbr\u003e\n1. From the Profile Chooser, tap on \u003cstrong\u003eSet up Multiple Profile\u003c/strong\u003es.\u003cbr\u003e\n2. Create a PIN and \u003cstrong\u003eSave\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n3. Fill in all fields for the profile.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; a. (Optional) Upload a photo.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; b. Enter a name.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; c. (Optional) Assign a 3-digit PIN.\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Tap \u003cstrong\u003eCreate\u003c/strong\u003e. This profile is added to your Profile Chooser!\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nIf you have created a profile before and have a PIN:\u003cbr\u003e\n1. From the Profile Chooser, tap on \u003cstrong\u003eAdd Profile\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n2. Enter your PIN and tap \u003cstrong\u003eSubmit\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n3. Fill in all fields for the profile.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; a. (Optional) Upload a photo.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; b. Enter a name.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u0026nbsp; c. (Optional) Assign a 3-digit PIN.\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Tap \u003cstrong\u003eCreate\u003c/strong\u003e. This profile is added to your Profile Chooser!\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nNote: Only the \u003cu\u003eAdministrator\u003c/u\u003e is able to manage profiles.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_2">\u003cp\u003eOnce a profile is deleted:\u003cbr\u003e\n- The profile cannot be recovered.\u003cbr\u003e\n- Profile information such as name, photos, and progress will be permanently deleted.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nTo delete a profile (excluding the \u003cu\u003eAdministrator\'s\u003c/u\u003e):\u003cbr\u003e\n1. From the Administrator\'s Home Page, tap on the menu button on the top left.\u003cbr\u003e\n2. Tap on \u003cstrong\u003eAdministrator Controls\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n3. Tap on \u003cstrong\u003eEdit Profiles\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Tap on the Profile you would like to delete.\u003cbr\u003e\n5. At the bottom of the screen, tap \u003cstrong\u003eProfile Deletion\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n6. Tap \u003cstrong\u003eDelete\u003c/strong\u003e to confirm deletion.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nNote: Only the \u003cu\u003eAdministrator\u003c/u\u003e is able to manage profiles.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_3">\u003cp\u003eTo change your email/phone number:\u003cbr\u003e\n1. From the Administrator\'s Home Page, tap on the menu button on the top left.\u003cbr\u003e\n2. Tap on \u003cstrong\u003eAdministrator Controls\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n3. Tap on \u003cstrong\u003eEdit Account\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nIf you want to change your email:\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Enter your new email and tap \u003cstrong\u003eSave\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n5. A confirmation link is sent to confirm your new email. The link will expire after __ days and must be clicked on to be associated with your account.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nIf changing your phone number:\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Enter your new phone number and tap \u003cstrong\u003eVerify\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n5. A code is sent to confirm your new number. The code will expire after __ minutes and must be entered in the new screen to be associated with your account.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_4">\u003cp\u003eOppia \"\u003cem\u003eO-pee-yah\u003c/em\u003e\" (Finnish) - \"to learn\"\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nOppia\'s mission is to help anyone learn anything they want in an effective and enjoyable way.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nBy creating a set of free, high-quality, demonstrably effective lessons with the help of educators from around the world, Oppia aims to provide students with quality education \u2014 regardless of where they are or what traditional resources they have access to.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nAs a student, you can begin your learning adventure by browsing the topics listed on the Home Page!\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_5">\u003cp\u003eAn Administrator is the main user that manages profiles and settings for every profile on their account. They are most likely your parent, teacher, or guardian that created this profile for you.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nAdministrators have the ability to manage profiles, assign PINs, and change other settings under their account. Depending on your profile, Administrator permissions may be required for certain features such as downloading Topics, changing your PIN, and more.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nTo see who your Administrator is, go to the Profile Chooser. The first profile listed and has \"Administrator\" written under their name is the Administrator.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_6">\u003cp\u003eIf the Exploration Player is not loading\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nCheck to see if the app is up to date:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Go to the Play Store and make sure the app is updated to its latest version\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nCheck your internet connection:\u003cbr\u003e\n- If your internet connection is slow, try re-connecting to your Wi-Fi network or connecting to a different network.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nAsk the Administrator to check their device and internet connection:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Get the Administrator to troubleshoot using the steps above\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nLet us know if you still have issues with loading:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Report a problem by contacting us at admin@oppia.org.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_7">\u003cp\u003eIf your audio is not playing\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nCheck to see if the app is up to date:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Go to the Play Store and make sure the app is updated to its latest version\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nCheck your internet connection:\u003cbr\u003e\n- If your internet connection is slow, try re-connecting to your Wi-Fi network or connecting to a different network. Slow internet may cause the audio to load irregularly, making it difficult to play.\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nAsk the Administrator to check their device and internet connection:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Get the Administrator to troubleshoot using the steps above\u003cbr\u003e\n\u003cbr\u003e\nLet us know if you still have issues with loading:\u003cbr\u003e\n- Report a problem by contacting us at admin@oppia.org.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_8">\u003cp\u003eTo download an Exploration:\u003cbr\u003e\n1. From the Home Page, tap on a Topic or Exploration.\u003cbr\u003e\n2. From that Topic Page, tap on the \u003cstrong\u003eInfo\u003c/strong\u003e tab.\u003cbr\u003e\n3. Tap on \u003cstrong\u003eDownload Topic\u003c/strong\u003e.\u003cbr\u003e\n4. Depending on your app settings, you may need Administrator approval or stable Wifi connection to complete your download. If needed, once these requirements are satisfied, the Topic has been downloaded onto the device and can be used offline by all profiles.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
  <string name="faq_answer_9">\u003cp\u003eIf you cannot find your question or would like to report a bug, contact us at admin@oppia.org.\u003c/p\u003e</string>
</resources>
